[Music]
In the name of God, the second session of teaching the
topic, continuing the topic of
kings and their types, as you
saw in the previous session, we
talked about the types of kings, and according to the same
schematic that we had, we came to the types of kings.
First, we talked about
what kind of kings are there on the chart, with what
types of types
in the area of ​​the breakdown area, before the breakdown area and
after the breakdown area, this seeking
was actually there. Now, each of these
was also categorized. Finally,
the brain of these kings was in the breakdown area. They had
swaps that we also
displayed. One topic was the confirmation of kings
that we had, which we showed after the
end of the body reaches its peak, and then from
that area that starts to rise and
is broken again by the price of the minor ones, we
consider it as confirmation of kings, and we
showed examples on the chart
that we will review today. Now, from the view,
because it was a discussion, then we came to the details of the
kings. We considered the details of when from high
to low rise.
Then we came to the area.
We drew the upper origin, the lower origin, based on that gold chart
and here, now its opening,
which we
need to penetrate and breach the range of this king.
Today, we will continue our discussion until the
topic we reached in the
previous session was, well, let's
talk a little about Holzm, let's open Holzm a little,
so first, we want to draw Holdo, let's say about it, which
of these two types of kinks is
more important to you, now the
third type of kink that is above the breakout area
is considered, but most of our work is
now on this area, so
first, there is a king, now whether it
is in the breakout area or before the breakout area,
then after the price is confirmed by this king, it goes
out of it, after entering the
king and the hole
by this king, the price must again hit one
higher than the ones that came into the cake,
here, that is, it returns and hits one higher, then
we say, well, the kink that we have here,
now the blue color is this
king that we have here, the price has held the price, it has known
one higher if
these that  Back into the price,
take the higher ones, that is, listen to the previous ones. We call it
holding. Well, this
can be
inside the breakout area. It can be before
and it can be after. Now, so to speak,
after the breakout area.
Now, they consider a fake level on the
breakout area
and before the breakout area. Well, there
are other special terms that we
consider as breakout decisions and now, Ars Field or LSF.
Now, as we talk about it in the discussions a little further ahead of
this topic, we
now realized that the money is made by the
inner area. Well, this inner area
is very different from here, except that we
have to look for an order. We don't have a specific one,
but it has to be in the wish area.
Now, this order may be here. It may be
by an area of ​​the chapter on a larger scale.
This is how we will talk about it now.
When you look at the details of the other orders, you will understand
what area the price can
return to and under what conditions.
This is
something that we will consider about these holds.
Now, let's go to some examples of holds with the areas
that are on our chart.  Let's look at each other and
go back to the four. Well,
one by one, there was
another case about this. There was another case
about the king. Now, after these
holds that I showed, we're talking about
here. Now, we have two. Now, the price has been
broken by this king on the area after the
price broke back inside. There was a price gap here.
Maybe it was at the beginning of the week or at
the end of the
market time. This gap occurred.
After the price returned inside the blue king, it
held and went up a leg. These types of
kings are considered hold for us after we
make a leg. Now, other examples of
RAM that we'll examine together, for example, the
example of the three bets before us does not have this hold. For
example, here, here is an example of a
hold in the broken area where the king 17 was
made on the king's break. The price found an exit from it, exited the
king, re-entered the
king, held, and the price was able to
register another levy here and come back. And this king
moved. Now, the king number that was before the
broken area and the king number that was after 4 after the
area.  It broke and didn't break our break line again. It went
up and came back. Let's go to the
next picture here. Well,
as you can see, in this picture, there
was a break in the past. The price here crossed the
line again and
made a king line. The
king made a break.
As the opening, the hold was done.
The price held here.
After the price went back from these highs, it was
able to
make a higher high so that it would come
into the area where it should break again.
King said, "I held it." So, on the
left, the soup itself is
important to us. And you can see that this red box
that crossed the blue line
made a kink. It came back and
came back down. It held the price but did
n't hold. King number three also broke this low.
That means before this low was formed,
there was a price gap between number E and the red and orange numbers. Usually,
these areas are good areas.  That is a level that is
created as liquidity before the area
and comes to form a larger one for a larger area.
When our blue box breaks from the left,
this new red box is formed
and this new red box has a smaller box in
itself
for it here
towards the orange area A. Now, so to speak,
this level has been broken. This is the Mars Mask and
ahead of
this area as the same level that was broken.
To create the red box, we have the
box resulting from the breakdown of this kink area on the left.
And in our chart, we have to consider a series of kings,
which we consider as the breakout areas.
Now, let's think about it. Well,
these kings, we will
return to them. These are some kings of
these areas.
Let's go to other areas, for example, here is a
ping in the broken area and the price after leaving the
red box has returned inside and
recorded a low here, so to speak, it has done the same holding.
Well, let's go to one of these A
here,
this is the one that is number
one, also one as a breakdown on the area and the
seventh as a king that is held in our schematics.
This kink is a kink that is before the
area, that's what we see in the schematic.
Some of our holds are related to
kings that are before the area.
This number 8 here, so we have a king
before the high breaks. After this
king breaks, so-called
breakdown lungs are formed, but it is held by the king
below the breakdown area, which is what
we call the DPs
that we are explaining about, meaning before the low and high, there
are kings that break. Decisions are made
inside them. We use it as a DP debacle.
After these highs break, the
price goes back inside and these hold.
Now in the pictures we had,
this is one of those examples. This king
breaks before the low and when the price goes back down, it is
held by this king and creates a low.
[Music] Let's
go to the
next example. Well, this is
a
swap and swap area. We don't identify it with a hold
.  This Kinga, which is mostly the Kinga that I had
broken before, but they didn't have a hold,
but this Kinga that was broken before, which is
number 8, I don't know. Number 8 here is an
example of number 8,
which is before the highs were broken and
causes the price to hit this high once,
this high, and we consider it as a hole, and the
swap and kink that breaks this will be important for us
in the future. We want to
buy things on them and do a trading plan on them. So the
next example here is this, this is a kind of
kink, kink, swap, and
but the Kinga soup before the break.
First, let me show you the drama, then we'll come back
to it. Well,
look at this No Kinga number 6. We had a way
here, one of which is that the blue color broke higher
in the reversal, which this red color took the form of a one.
Now let's go back to the
chart. Well, here we have
these highs broken
by the Inkin King.
Then the price in the sheet is in the
red box, and in the future it could
be a place for the price to reverse.  Here is an example, then
this is also this is a type of kink
number 8 example where this low is broken. The kink before the
break and the price returns to this. Here is
another example of kink number 8.
After the break of this low, the price makes a move.
This king is
on the broken level that it has held, which in this case
gives a swap, which we will talk about in the discussion now.
This kink king number
8 is the
price holding the area before this, now it will hold this area again in the future.
The whole area is based on the
[music]
price of the events that occur on the chart and the reason
why an area holds the price several times.
And now this is what we
talked about in the first lesson. Now let's go back to the
paint and the chart to talk about a topic here.
We have
some areas on our chart
with
these kings that we talked about. There are
a series of areas where the price is
on the market, that is,  There is not enough time for that or
because there is too much momentum now, there is
not enough time for those areas to return. For example, if we assume
here that there is a kink here, the
price with the momentum that has just
broken in this area, the price could not do that
drop-base drop at the moment of the drop-base rally at the
moment to create a king.
Some of these areas are inverted on the chart.
That is, if you assume that you have a low
here, a low one high,
a low lower, then this
lower low is broken by a king here, and
on the way back, this king is
now hit with momentum or with a candle that
was very powerful, a candle one piece here.
This king, in other words, the
price could not break through a king and it goes
away. Now it returns to it in a larger structure,
which we will talk about in the future
.  He goes one, hits one or two
from above, then returns to
this area and moves again.  We now
want to talk about these types of kings in the
charts we have.
These are the so-called
areas that have
not failed and the price will return
to them in the future.
This is an example, for example, we have this green line, the price has
broken this red line, the lumo has broken, and a
red box has been created. You can see that
here, when returning, with a single
candle with broken momentum, there is also a kink that has been
created,
that is, it has not returned to the breakdown area here, and it has
created a liquidity level for now, which
the price will come in the future, this area has been
broken and has gone higher again.
These kings are now a good place to
collect liquidity below them, that is,
many traders want to empty this area
and come again
below this kink that has been broken above the level. You
can see here that there is a gap that has
not returned, so now create a scenario before it
and make an F in this area and
continue its movement again. We have these types of kings.
For example, here, you look at a lumo,
a king has been created, but in
the return, there is no king structure in these areas,
that is, in the lower areas.
What is the price of a single candle for this entire
path?  The price has returned after returning to this
area a few times. Now it has been in this area and has
started moving again and has crossed this ceiling.
Well,
here is another kink that you look at here. The
kink that caused it to break out here. Now I'm going to draw my diagram
next to it. The kink that caused it to break out here.
On the way back, a piece has left here. You can see that it has
gone up here. The area has broken out. The area has broken out. These are the highs.
And in
the future, the price has come to the broken level and Majd has
recorded a higher high here again. This
is our area. Now, these areas sometimes
align with a lap shoulder or higher time zones, which we will examine now
.  See, right now we are finding examples of these
kings on the chart that break with
spike candles or with high momentum in the reversal
.   Another
example that you look at here is one where there is
no soup structure here at all in the upper edge reversal.
For example, this
situation and the price has crossed these again with momentum
and in the reversal now here this
area because it usually does not have a breakout level is a
good place to mislead the trend and usually
for now the kind of view that we take is
not that we want to set a stop loss based on this low and these highs
now,
not our stops based on this low but
well the entry always has to go now look at the
breakout here and this kink that occurs before that
breakout usually this kink is before
our breakout i.e. it becomes our entry point
this kinky gig range exists before the breakout
and the stop loss is below the low that was
created now we will talk more about how to trade these
but for now we need to know what
these kinks are and what they do
this is another type of kink that now the price has
not broken here in the reversal but here the price has made
a comeback to this area but here it has
not broken structure
once it has gone out inside  And the
higher ones in the reversal of a broken beat, well the
kink that you see here is now the rune of the
break and caused the price to move
up the holding price.
Look at the next example, like here, a
kink that held and hit the higher ones
in the reversal, there was no breakdown structure in this
single candle. Well, there is a technique here that I will
tell you that because I
often use this tactic in these areas.
Because you are looking here now,
I will draw a schematic of it.
There is a link on the left, a way to make a
leg hit in the reversal of a broken beat. Usually,
this area that
you should draw from the left is
that this is exactly where
this circle is, a single candlestick, a
one-minute candlestick that
you may have, for example, from here up to this area, that
single candlestick, that is, a T in the
form of a candlestick started from here and
continued until here. So what is this tactic?
You take this single candlestick. It comes up a lot of
times. For example, I say, you expect.
It should hit the blue edge exactly, but
the market is coming and going inside this single candle,
now it doesn't reach that edge a bit, and you're
going to fit in here, and the price is going to fall again.
For this, when these
break sharply in these areas that
hold, we choose the broken single candle, this low, this high, this low, this low, all
together, for
our entry point, but our stop loss
should be on the I. Now these are optimized.
This staffing distance is not logical, but
the principles of the initial framework are as follows, which I will
now address.
This was the last photo. In this case, these are
examples that are now
broken
.  Well,
this is the complete set of our kings on the
chart. Now, some of the navamas that did
n't have kings. Now, let's go back to where we came from.
We talked about the details of the king, for example, how many areas does it have? An
upper origin, a lower origin, and swaps of
both of these. And next time, I want to
talk about the types of kings.
Where to place a door, what words do we want to
use in conversation?  Then let's break down those
names one by one and
consider their philosophical underpinnings.  The first issue is
that if a kink is located on the failure area, it
could be an arc.  That is, an
arc or an area, a retracement, and
sometimes
before the break, like the
number Hina before the high and low break, which
are called a series of decision-making points that we
call DP. If they hold once, they
fold this king once, which is
the nature of a
flag limit, meaning that after the
break, the price returns to this
area and holds it again, going up. I will consider these
as flags now. Then,
or about this left, which
means a high, a low, a higher high, and then a
lower low, here, I will
write this way: a high, a low, and a higher high, a higher high,
and a lower low, low.
Well, this alignment of these highs, I draw
a line from the method, and usually the kink that
forms on these highs is
considered as a left LS king, that is, a left shoulder king.
Now, sometimes,
when a lower low is exposed, it is exposed. Well,
this  The same Kim Lull comes back here
because he hit a low low. If Lu
doesn't hit a low low and comes back, and
our left shoulder king is hit and he has the ability to hold again, we'll discuss where he
came back from in the next sessions
.  For now, we're
calling this King K.S., and we're calling it a
Shoulder King Cup.  Here, the right lo is lower
and is known as QM Lolm.
Now, if I
draw a high here in the next pint, the price will break this high.
And again, I consider this as a
left when the price breaks
this left here and comes down. So
if it goes down a low and comes back down, it's the same as the left.
But if it goes down
below this low and comes back down, it
has a left shoulder kink here. We consider this king
as a left shoulder king
after this reversal.  Now, I'm going to
discuss where it
came from, and this is about learning DPs now,
because this was a decision to break these highs.
I'll explain more about it there. First, I'll explain the decision. Then, just
know that we now consider this king that is on
these highs and one higher high
as an
S king,
and the term
LS king in terms of the
lap shoulder king here, lap shoulder king.
Well, if the price of
this king falls before the break, it means that
we have a high right now, and when this I-
market comes, it will make a kink before this I
and break again with this one.  Well, this
kink that is no different before the defeat of this high or low
.  I'm giving an ascending example now.  This is my
descending example.  For example, you
have a position like this
and the price
comes back before it breaks this area.
Or you can have this other than this low. It
can be a kink here. There is a
kink here. This king
here. The price comes before it
hits the area.
This king is considered as a
decision to break this area.
Now, what is the position of this king itself?
And I do
n't know because we are very much on this king dip
or as a decision or a dpi. We
identify these kings. Or this
king that is here. I said that it hits either a high
or a
here as a dpi.
This is another low.
Well, we identify these kings as dpi.
What is the position of this? Can a
bridge be built under them or not?
When will we use it? All of this
should be discussed in the next meetings.
You can only see now that the king that is formed before this high, this
king, is
considered as a dpi. Well,
many people are asking questions now. Well, sir,
I  For example, let's come to a chart now
and if you consider a low like this
low and before this low you want to get a break, it wo
n't be seen in this time frame.
But if the time frame, for example, we want to get the king
before this low,
leave it as it is.
If we take the time frame, take it one time higher,
this won't be seen, this will be the kink. If we
take it one time higher again, this won't be seen,
this will be the kink.
Well, we have a series of frameworks of principles and
rules for this now, how to
get this king,
how to get it, so that we don't want to
consider these as fractals anymore because it is
very related to the left side, but what is
specific now, for example, for this low that has been
broken here, I will draw a line now,
so I will cut here
and come here, now the low that has been broken before this area,
this a, this low, there is a
king here,
now we don't need this one,
here is
who was the guardian of this low.  Broken and we
consider this low as a decision. Now,
in the price reversal, when this kink is
broken, then we take a view. Then we
need to know what this king is
before it was formed before this low and
what is important to us in the reversal
and what kind of key, what word do we
use to call it? Decision as a
DP or
decision point here and hitting this area
creates a view for us. Not always,
very often these are the
notes that need to be hit and this
goes back to now, much, much further discussions
and maybe in the
[music] room.
[music]
Now, let's go back to this type of kink that
we drew here as a decision.
To break this low, well, let's consider one of the
kings' positions as a left shoulder king, for example. Let's
see here if we can draw a
left shoulder, a line from this, that is,
draw a line from this low here and
consider this as a low
and here is a high and a low.  Lower it down, Lo
Lo, and here it becomes a higher high, this king for
us, Kink Lap Shoulder King. Now after the
price passes this high, if it returns to this, it will be
a Kim Pipes Low Low, and if it
returns to this area before this high, then
the story is just an Elsep Wing, a Left Shoulder
King. Here we have it, which has
not become a Kim anymore, and before that, now by hitting
the decision that hit this Low, it will return to this
area and continue its path
.  So, so far we have understood that we
consider this king as an alt king.
Now I don't want it to be a
higher high or a leaked one. For example, I don't want to give too much away about this. But you know, this kink that is in line with the relo is an alt sync here. Or, for example, if you look at the top of the chart,
if this one high, one high and one
higher high here, for example, as a line, if
we put these highs, this king as an
alt sync that we are considering. Now, this
can again be, for example, this fractal.
For example, if you have a high here, it's not that
you think all of this works.
No, these have a series of conditions and rules. That levy that
goes does a series of things. Its left shoulder is
important for us. Now,
this is it. Now, in the discussion of
areas, for example, let's go into more detail. I
say, we'll examine its structure. We
examined this structure here. So, we'll examine it
now. So, one before it
broke.  We consider the failure zone as an elkskin
.  Now look, we
have a lock here again, so what broke this lock?
That this was his decision, a
decision that broke this mold as a
decision.  Well, we'll come back later, but this
decision won't work.  Yes, we will categorize these logs
.  A Levi that is the result of a
reaction, a Levi that is the result of a breakdown, a Levi that we are
now marking so that we
can identify them one by one.  So let's go back
to this area where the price came and broke it, and
now
here we have a low and a high, and the price
started from here and came up. If
you look here again, there is a left that has lows and
lows here.
After the price opened the upper area,
it returned to this
left. So now we have learned how to
draw these areas
.  Well, I'm drawing water,
and now the price could
go up again from this area.
So
let's go back to our diagram that was here. Now
this example is
bullish and this example is bearish. So the position
that this king has in line with this low low
and lower low is as the LS in the
perspective of highs and higher highs as the LS Def
Shoulder Kinke or the position that we used to
consider as the opening in previous periods.  This as EL, this
as ORIGIN, but now I do
n't even want to put words on it.  Now I'm going to say
a skinning shoulder lift. This is because
we only have two types of setups. We trade a lot.
Two notes. One is based on these
symmetrical highs. One is based on decision areas.
Now, liquidity and decision areas are more.
Well, that's what we need to do with the pauses and our decision. It will
help us to master them.
Now,
let's move on. We also
have some rallies that are on the compression areas.
First, we need to teach the compression itself. Then, let's
talk about these kings that are on the compression areas. So, this is like
in the CP time. Now, let's learn about the compression of an
area first. Let's learn what this is. What is
this shoulder lift? Then,
this is a brief summary. When we learn them, here we learn what
parameters a compression wave has. In order for us to
identify them, most of these areas
should be on the F side or the E side. Now, as the
price turns, those areas are the EPO. We
also used the term "wolf up." In the
next session, we will also teach them.  So
far, we have identified all our kinks. We
have this series of kinks and we work with them.
Kinks that exist before compression
and are formed along with compression areas. Let's
review our
left shoulder kinks once again and there is a series of kinks
called before failure and after failure.   This
means that there is a break here
and the kings that are now in the broken area must
hold.
Now, let's talk about a few examples in the chart
and then return to the
topic of the continuation of the discussion.  So this was the decision
that was made here, the price returned to this area
and started to rise above this area again.
Now let's go back to
[music].
Examples that exist here, for example. Now
some of these are like here. Well, we'll take a few
examples of these kings before they broke. Look, for example,
we have a low here, a low here,
a low here. All three of these
levies that exist here, if I draw a line through them,
this low and this one, it's clear that they've
crossed this one. All three were broken by this king,
meaning they were hit below this area. After this,
as a king, the price made a decision after
hitting the back of the area, now it's back to
this left that it has here and continues its
upward path.  I want these examples so
that we know how we can make decisions
in fear.  For example, here now if
you look at a Levi that has a Low here,
a Low here that is now here that is itself
called a kink, a kink that has held the price, this
Low here is a kink that was formed before this,
here as a decision
after the break, the price returns to it and
holds again downwards. Well, so
this area was held. Now we want to go into some
examples. Just
one point that we want to talk about now,
these kings before the break that we identified as DPs,
I want to say that we always
bring in our picture now that we
expect that from any Low
or any that a kink has been created before it,
and this King that
we identified as a DP, that is, we identified as a DP, it will
hold the price on the first return.
Many times this does not happen on the chart.
So if we want to
go into a little more detail on this,
that is, to know why some of them are not and some are,
well, I need a little discussion ahead, that is, is there
behind this area?  We'll
consider this as a violation or when it
hits its back, for example, well, we shouldn't
take a view on this. This will be left up front, but
first, let's look at the position that this king himself takes
when he breaks this line.
So, what position can this have
that we can take into account?
If the price turns or does this area
hold the price if it was a level when it hit it,
consider it as a violation or
immediately without holding it, it is hit
or hit below it. Consider these
points. We should add to it. Well, this
kink area that exists before the break,
can it have a better position? Yes,
if we look at many cases on the chart,
this price on the left side here can be the
result of nothing or it can be the result of a lift.
These are the ones you should pay attention to.
For example, if we have a lefty here,
excuse me. Here, for example, if there is a lefty,
this area here has a lefty
and there are some highers. Well,
if it is in line with that, then it can be in a
suitable position. Or sometimes
this result itself, for example, now I'm
coming down a bit. The
result of the failure is a kind of its own. You
have this
low here again. Assume that the low here is here.
That top is the result in line with this.
In this lower area, well, in this upper area,
when the price goes up.  Yink has
made a reversal here and when this breaks,
this kink before it was the result of a kink, that is, we
should pay attention to it. This can be, for
example, in the example on the right, the result of nothing.
These highs hit
in the example here, the result of, for example,
a line with a low that hit this low.
In the
example that is now in a downward trend, you
have a low here. Here is a low. The price
has gone up, meaning Riches has gone up. Then there was a
kink here that this high recorded.
Now either in or the first kink that formed after the low.
These highs formed a shape or
sometimes this itself has a fractal, meaning you
look here. For example, now I will make this a little more
complicated. Here is the breakdown itself. This is the
breakdown of a low here.
Well, here is the lemon.
Here is the lemon. The price of baking that it made
went up. In the return of
this king, as a decision, the low was broken. Well,
these are the
details. Now, I looked at the kink that I came to before my cut. Is it a
kink that is the result of nothing that the high hit a
kink before?  A break on a low that acted,
a left that did not act, or a kink that
swapped on a king. So these are the three cases. We
should identify these in the chart as
a decision. If we identify the break of the low and the
high, these kings before the break, then
this is the type of this. Let me come back to it again. There is
nothing in more detail. Is it the result of a left, for example, a left
that did not act here?
I will write this decision now. For example, this can be done
here. It can be another because
and this is the third type.
Here is the third type. For example, in our type one, one is
that without any
gap, no reaction has formed here. In two, not
in the low on the low that we had here. For example, the low on the low that we had here,
the one that we had here, and the low on the low that we
had here. Here, the
price has returned to this
area. There was no reaction. There was no tendency for this to be a low on the low. The
price is returning
here. Now we expect that in this
box, the price will go down or in the type of
number here, we expect the price to go down
after the reaction. Number one here, we
also expect a reaction. Are there expectations?  In all
three of these, it's the same. Well, some of the answers are
different. That is, the function of this is that the
low alignment, number two, can be a stronger place.
In number three, it can be a better place.
In number one, it can be fragile, for example,
it can hit below this.
So let's consider these three situations for the kings that are
before the low and high. We
call these DPs. But is this DP itself in a
suitable position that we expect the price to return from
or not? Now let's go to
this number three. It has more details.
Now, we will add number three in the topic that we will
add in the future. On the tone of
our negation, which we haven't talked about yet, we
will discuss number three more. Number three. Now, let's
go back to the chart. Let's
look at a few examples of this together. For example, here, where we just came
in gold as a one,
here, I'll bring you
the annotate.
This area where we came in, we
said, well, here we
have an area. Now, there was a low that we
had here. The price came from this kein that
broke here. Which one is this from?  Of those three
cases, well, as you look at it, this
king is in line with the resistance area, so
here
we have a king here,
so this is the cougar, which group of this area can be
part of number three, see exactly, it can be
part of number three. Now, this can be part of number
E. Sometimes, this line is in line with an area.
[Music]
Now, let's go in line, for example, with a left, let's
find it in the four here.
Now, there is a kink here, and we
have some here, some here,
well, the kink that exists before the breakdown.
This is the question that arises here. Is the
result of the breakdown something that we expect
the price to return from, for example, this is the
number one example, so when the number
one example is here, then this acts differently,
and those areas that are in line or are
in line, then this can be, for example, the price
now crosses this area and reaches a lower level.
Sometimes, this line is in line with
an
area, for example, a left or now I have the example, for example,
in the
other.  I'll show you an example of a time frame below that's in
my mind now, between here
now as a
saying, look here, let me
find an example of this piece.   So
now here, for example, I wanted to give an example, for
example, here is a low that is aligned with a high, here is
a low that has broken, the price is at a high, now let's see
this candlestick a little bit, oh, let's put a
mark here, let's
take it higher
[music],
blink, well, I'll bring it a little bit, the
inverter will show up, so look here, we have a left, a low,
one high, one high,
one high, if you look here,
I'll put a line here, so we have one,
before the break, this low
exists as an area in one here, which
is aligned with this left area, meaning from this
left, if we have a line, it's also right, that
in addition to the number, for example, two in this
image that we had here, there is also number two, number three,
meaning it's aligned with number three.
Now I'm going to go back to the chart
here, for example, we have that Kingo
here, which means this area is
now also aligned
with this area, with a left.  Well, that's because he has a levee
that's broken here on the lower scale, so you
have to look at this in detail
.
Here I will explain again, there is a
lefty here, a low down here, well, the
kink that happens here before the break, this kink
before the break is in line with that low.
Look, we have a kink here that is on this
area, so the range where the price
breaks this low as a decision is in this
area. This area itself is a
low in the reflex.
If you look at it again, this way, this is
finally where we have a low, one low, these three lows that have been
broken, and a decision has been formed on this area
for all three. We must consider the price when it breaks
this low in this
area as a
price reversal. Now, here, I have to show the
lower timeframe and
put here, here, the line that comes from here.
This single candlestick that
I put a line from here. This single candlestick that
is here is
for making a decision
to break this low or in line with that
lefty. This is an example. Now, there are
other examples. For example, here,
if we look at these, this is as a
decision to  Broken, well we have to see if
this is the result of something or not on its own. Now
this could be the result of this one whose opposite is
here, that is, here.
So this one that was broken here by this. Now
look at this
broken range. The price held it here once, twice,
then broke it again. Now I want to make a
decision with that.
Now we have a low here. It broke. Well, this low was
broken by a pinky in this area. That is,
a kink here. Is this kink
here the
result of an area? But if we
look at this here,
when the price broke this, then it chatted here.
That is, it was an area that
was at the beginning of the day or at the same time that there was
this chat. The range that
this decision that broke this low. Now
here we come and say, what broke our blue box
?
A range that is above it, for example,
look here, this area, this area, because there is
no information, now I will make an assumption for you, so there was
a king here, so this king
went up in its death, the price came, this
king that was here made a decision, and at
the same time this low was broken, and our
expected range from here means the return that
the price has after the break, and we
as a decision, this decision can be a place
that our expectation is a solid place and the
result of a
decision and indecision, now we will
talk about the indecision in the next meeting, the
price returns to this, so don't forget this case, now let's
summarize and review the
discussions that were in this group meeting
and the exercises,
well, the cases that we talked about, one was the hold,
where to hold and the
return,
well, the second case was a series of kings that did
not break, and those kings that did not break,
now we came and examined them together,
and the case that was now naming these
kings, the kink that was
identified as a decision before the break  We do.
We came to this decision ourselves. Now,
the position of the previous kink, which we examined at all,
we said, could be a kink that is now the result of
nothing. But your expectations for these
areas should be different. The one that was
not the result of anything and we separated the data that
was the result of a limited failure for the failure of the low.
Then we came to the position of the
king position that we named on a left.
We said, here can be an ace king
or the cakes that are now before the compression fracture.
Now, we didn't explain about it. We
left this on the topic of
compression until we get to it. Now, the exercises that we
are planning for the next session. Now, these
decisions and this laptop. I don't want to
say, for example, which one is going to penetrate these.
Now, because we didn't talk about the golf at all, in the
next session, we want to
talk about the indecision. Come later. Because when there is a decision, there
is also an indecision. That is, the same word as ignore. Let's
talk about that. Then, let's talk about the
defect. That is, the golfs. Oh, that will come later.
For example,  Let's say this lift that you
are considering here, one is that the sousha should
have this area, just so that our
eyes can learn. For now, we are looking at the chart
as an
algorithm. When we get to the details,
every lift will no longer work for us. For example, that one will
not work for us. We will separate the symmetry of the left.
Based on what the high and
low did, so let's do some exercises. Now, let's
take some examples of these cases. One is this
lift, then the decision-making before its breakdown, and
examples of the decisions itself. That is, is this
decision the result of a swap-swap breakdown or the
result of not reacting to a lift or not, the result of nothing,
before the high is broken. Let's
examine which one can
be stronger for the return and the expectation that
the price will return.
Now, take care of all these exercises.
Post them in the journals. The
next session will be uploaded by the end of the week. The next session will also
have a lot of detailed discussions about this indecision and the in-golf and F&Ps.
God willing, we will see what happens.  Good
morning, in the name of God, I greet you and have a good time.
Dear friends and companions, we are
very happy to be with you with the new trading
course of the Zeus Group.  This
course is published in its entirety in a dedicated playlist
of the same name on Zeus' official YouTube page at
Zeus Forex Channel, and all
sessions can be viewed in order from the first episode
.  In this course, you will see 9 one-hour teaching sessions
presented conceptually and practically.  After watching each session, you can
practice and then watch 6
short half-hour troubleshooting sessions of friends
who participated in the course to
get a better understanding of the material. After that,
enter the next teaching session. To communicate
directly with us and use the troubleshooting plans,
simply send a message to Zeus Group's Telegram ID on
this admin's line and stay in touch with us
.  Wishing you all success in your
trading career, my dears.
[Music]